请举起你的右手  跟着我说
Please raise your right hand and repeat after me.
我  唐纳德·约翰·特朗普  郑重宣誓
I, Donald John Trump, do solemnly swear...
我  唐纳德·约翰·特朗普
I, donald john trump,
郑重宣誓
do solemnly swear...
我必忠实执行
...that I will faithfully execute...
合众国总统之位
...the office of president of the...
不清楚考试时间安排的听好
Those of you unclear about the schedule,
今天考试内容分为两部分
Today's portion of the exam will consist of two sections.
每部分将有三个小时作答时间
You will have three hours to complete each one.
对考试有存疑之处的...
Anything that's unclear on the exam...
伊利诺州司法考试
光之墅
普罗旺斯  150万欧元
查询结果
玛娅·林德尔
还未有司法考试结果  请稍后重试
伊利诺州司法考试委员会
伊利诺州司法考试结果页面
你的司法考试结果
通过
玛娅·林德尔
怎么  怎么了
What? What's wrong?
我是律师了
I'm a lawyer.
亲爱的
Oh, babe.
我的天
Oh, my God!
我是律师了
I'm a lawyer!
我是律师了  我的天
I'm a lawyer. Oh, my God.
我要辞职
I'm resigning.
去哪儿
To go where?
哪也不去
Nowhere.
我要退休了
I'm retiring.
我的天
Oh, my god.
什么时候
When?
两周后
Two weeks.
我不会给你们留个烂摊子
I don't want to leave you in the lurch.
所以  我会等肯德尔案结了以后
So, I'll just, uh, finish out the Kendall case.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
我们头重脚轻了
We're top heavy.
八个冠名合伙人
Eight name partners.
我准备过自己的生活了
I'm ready to live my life.
写本回忆录  放松一下
Write a memoir, take a deep breath.
恭喜你  戴安
Congratulations, Diane.
谢谢  大卫
Thank you, David.
洛哈特&德克尔&古斯曼&李&莱曼&吉尔伯特·卢瑞&卡跟&坦纳鲍姆律所
早上好  洛哈特&德克尔&古斯曼&李
Good morning. Lockhart, Deckler, Gussman, Lee,
莱曼&吉尔伯特·卢瑞&卡根&坦纳鲍姆律所
Lyman, Gilbert-Lurie, Kagan, Tannebaum & Associates,
请问您找谁
how may I direct your call?
我听说他们第一个月就会解雇一半的人
I heard they fire half of us in the first month.
没错  我也听说了
Oh, yeah, yeah, I heard that, too.
我们应该团结起来
We should stick together.
我叫莉莉
Uh, I'm Lili.
玛娅
Maia.
戒指真好看
Uh, pretty ring.
什么戒指
What is it?
这是念珠戒指
Oh, it's a rosary ring.
你信教吗
Are you religious?
不  不信
No, no.
只是紧张而已
Just nervous.
站起来
Stand up!
这些是给客户坐的椅子
Those seats are for clients.
跟我来  试着跟上节奏
Follow me and try to keep up.
洛哈特&德克尔&李律所是由三家
Lockhart, Deckler, Lee is the result of a merger
中等规模的律所合并而来
of three mid-sized firms.
我们现在是中西部拥有最多民事律师的律所
We are now the largest civil litigator in the midwest,
能来这里是你们的荣幸
and you are lucky to be here.
作为一名新律师  你们随时会被解雇
As new associates, you can be fired at any time,
你们中很多人会被解雇
and many of you will be.
看看你周围的人
Look at the person next to you.
他们都是你的竞争对手
They are your competitor.
你要么比他们强  要么走人
Do better than them, or you're gone.
这不是律师集训营
This is not lawyer camp.
我们不是来帮你们学习的
We are not here to help you learn.
你们是来为我们效力的
You are here to help us.
如果合伙人有衣服要拿去干洗
If a partner needs their dry-cleaning,
你的态度要像在帮肯尼迪大法官做助手一样
treat it like a clerkship for Justice Kennedy.
肯尼迪大法官：美国最高法院大法官
有什么问题
Any questions?
这里是档案库房
This is a depo dump.
我们需要知道这里的85632份文件
We need to know what is in every one of these
都是什么
85,632 documents.
叫到名字的往前站
Come forward when I call your name.
迈克尔·贝尔
Michael Baer.
-我在哪儿办公  -大卫·柳
- Uh, where do I work? - David Yoo.
朱迪·巴夏
Jodie Bashar
莉莉·布伦纳
Lili Brenner.
玛娅
Maia...
玛娅·林德尔
Maia Rindell?
你好啊  玛娅
How are you doing, Maia?
很好
Good.
不  不  你拿这些
No, no, no, here, you take these.
替我向你父母问好  好吗
Say hello to your parents for me, will you?
好的
Sure.
顺便一提  这是今早送来的
Oh, by the way, this came for you this morning.
博尔·费兰德
Burl Ferrand.
丽贝卡·卢扎托
Rebecca Luzzatto.
妈
Mom.
拜托别再给我送东西了  行吗
Please don't send me anything else, okay?
我很感谢  你知道的
Um, I appreciate it, you know I do,
但是  这样让我看起来
but, uh, it's making me look, um...
像有特权一样
I don't know, entitled.
其他人对你不好吗  亲爱的
Are people not being nice to you, dear?
不  妈妈  他们对我很好
No, mom, they're being great.
只是这样太引人关注了
It's the attention.
我只是想融入大家
You know, I want to just...blend in.
想让我叫戴安给你安排个办公室吗
Do you want me to ask Diane to put you in your own office?
别  妈妈  别这样  好吗
No, mom, no, please, okay?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
因为我们给戴安打个电话就行
Because we can call Diane.
不用  一切都好
No. Everything is fine.
好吧  我得先挂了
All right, we got to go.
我一会儿再和戴安确认
And, uh, I'll check in with Diane later.
不  妈妈  妈妈  不用的
No, mom-mom, it's okay.
爱你  宝贝儿
Love you, sweetheart.
早上好
Good morning.
洛哈特&德克尔&古斯曼&李&莱曼
Lockhart, Deckler, Gussman, Lee, Lyman,
吉尔伯特·卢瑞&卡根
Gilbert-Lurie & Kagan...
百合花已经够多了
Enough with the lilies.
要知道还是有人对花粉过敏的
You know, some of us have allergies.
我其实是新来的律师
Oh, I'm actually a new associate here.
那可真棒
Good for you.
通知你的首席花匠  别弄百合花过来了
Just go tell your head florist no more lilies.
是玛娅·林德尔吗
Maia Rindell?
任何东西都别碰
Don't touch anything.
也别乱坐
And don't sit.
戴安·洛哈特
玛娅
Maia.
你还好吗
How you doing?
我很好
Good, good.
这是你成为律师的第一天
Your first day as a lawyer.
你父母来了电话
Your parents called.
天呐  我叫他们别给你打电话的
Oh, god, I told them not to.
不  没关系的
No, it's all right.
他们担心你会受排斥
They're worried you might be being ostracized.
他们不能再这样了
Oh, they have got to stop.
-真的  -没关系
- Really... - It's okay.
楼下还有间空办公室  我可以
There is an empty office downstairs that I can...
-不  真不用  -别这样
- No, no, please. - Oh, come on,
-我不需要什么东西  -拜托
- I-I don't want anything. - Come on,
让教母好好溺爱一下你
let your godmother spoil you a little bit.
戴安  求你了
Diane, please.
好吧  天呐  你长大了
Okay. Oh God, you've grown.
是吗  我感觉自己又变成小孩了
Oh really? Oh, I feel like I've shrunk.
艾米还好吗
How's Amy?
她很好
Good, good.
她打算朝着检察长的位置发展
She's up for a bureau chief position.
我听说了
I heard.
我有东西要送给你
Listen, I have something for you.
这是珀尔·哈特给我的
This was given to me by Pearl Hart,
珀尔·哈特
芝加哥首位女性公诉辩护人
The first female public defender in Chicago.
现在是你的了
Now it's yours.
真的吗
Seriously?
我要退休了  而你刚起步
I'm retiring. You're starting.
送你这个很合适  如同权杖交接
It's fitting. Like a baton.
现在轮到你接班了
Now it's your turn to carry it.
可我什么都还没做
Oh, I haven't done anything yet.
我当时也没做什么
I hadn't, either.
而它会激励你  好吗
This will force you to, okay?
我还能做两周的导师  好好利用吧
Let's make the most of my two weeks left of mentoring.
旁听这次的取证  做点笔记
Take notes on this deposition.
我之后会问你  你认为我们应该
Afterwards, I'll ask you what you think
提出多少的和解费
we should offer as a settlement.
卢卡
Lucca.
洛哈特女士  你好
Ms. Lockhart. Hello.
我不知道你加入了雷迪克&博斯曼律所
I didn't know you joined Reddick & Boseman.
四个月前加入的
Four months ago.
艾丽西娅也在吗
Oh. Alicia, too?
不  只有我
No, just me.
恭喜你
Well, congratulations.
我们现在开始吗  还是
Shall we get started here, or do we...
戴安  抱歉我迟到了
Diane, sorry I'm late.
门罗法官在电梯里拦着我聊了会儿
Judge Monroe stopped me in the elevator.
大家还好吗
How is everyone?
戴安  真可惜
Daine, I feel so bad.
听说你要退休了
I heard you're retiring.
要输掉最后一个案子的感觉一定很糟
It's terrible you're gonna lose your last case.
博斯曼先生  你这话太出人意料了
Mr. Boseman, how unexpected.
我是哪边的人来着
So, which side am I on here?
点兵点将  大兵大将
Eeny...Meeny...
小兵小将
Miny...
好吧
Okay.
救命
Someone help!
放开他  放开他
Leave him alone! Leave him alone!
-我很难受  -放开他
- Ow, I'm sick! - Leave him alone!
我很难受  让我起来
I'm sick! Let me up!
让我起来
Let me up...
这视频是你拍的对吧  亨特先生
You shot that video, didn't you, Mr. Hunter?
-是的  -能告诉我们你看见了什么吗
- Yes. - Would you tell us what you saw?
我看到这些警察把托比按在地上
I saw these cops tackling Toby.
你指托比·肯德尔先生  这位受害者吗
And that would be Mr. Toby Kendall, the victim right here?
-反对受害者一词  -真的吗  戴安
- Objection as to victim. - Really, Diane?
这位先生已经坐在轮椅上了
The gentleman's in a wheelchair.
吃饭都得靠他父母喂
His parents have to feed him.
你想让我叫他什么
Now what do you want me to call him, um...
快乐的涉事人吗
Happy participant?
我接受被捕人这个称呼
Arrestee is good by me.
不行  你可以将你的反对意见记录在案
No, you can preserve your objection for the record,
但那可不是一位被捕者的样子
but that right there is no arrestee.
住手  住手  快住手
Stop! Stop! Stop it!
住手
Stop!
对托比·肯德尔头部的一脚
That kick to Toby Kendall's head,
完全是毫无缘由的攻击  对吗
that was completely unprovoked, am I right?
是的
Yeah.
托比只是躺在那而已
Toby just lay there.
该你了  戴安
All yours, Diane.
你提到原告的时候总是叫他托比
You keep referring to the plaintiff as Toby.
你认识托比吗
Do you know Toby?
你们是朋友吗
Are you friends?
我是不是该问博斯曼先生
Should I ask Mr. Boseman
-他是否想要回答这个问题  -反对
- if he wants to answer that question? - Objection.
好吧  我再问一遍
Okay, let me ask you again.
-你认识托比吗  -他是我的朋友
- Do you know toby? - He's a friend.
当晚你们是否合谋爆窃车辆
And were you together that night trying to break into cars?
我们没有爆窃任何东西
We didn't break into anything.
因为你们在得手前就被抓了
Because you were caught before you could...
反对  他已经回答过问题了
Objection. He's already answered the question.
阿德里安  你怎么不坐呀
Adrian, why don't you sit down?
因为我斗志昂扬
Because I'm too passionate.
好吧
Oh, okay.
亨特先生  这段视频
Uh, Mr. Hunter, this video.
阿德里安  麻烦倒回去一下
Adrian, would you mind rewinding?
-当然  -谢谢
- Sure. - Thanks.
请问这是
Is this...
录制的开始吗
the beginning of the recording here?
是的  你什么意思
Yeah, what-what do you mean?
你就是这时候打开摄像头的  这一刻
This is where you turned on your camera, right here?
用我手机  是的
My cell phone, yeah.
在这一刻之前没有其他镜头了吗
There was no other footage before this moment?
戴安  你要说什么
Diane, what do you have?
大家就别绕弯子了
Let's not sandbag here.
你知道你的视频是附带元数据的吗
Did you know that your video has metadata attached to it?
即使你试图删除视频  元数据仍然会显示
Even if you try to erase it, the metadata tells us
这段视频缺少了1分20秒
that there is one minute and 20 seconds missing
-就在片头的位置  -反对
- from the head of it. - Objection!
你觉得呢
Well?
400万
$4 million.
为什么
Why?
那段视频
The video.
很不利
It's bad.
客户要求我们把和解价格控制在50万以下
We've been asked to keep the settlement under $500,000.
-客户是  -库克县
- By... - Cook county.
他们前一任民事律所就因为大手大脚解雇了
They fired their last civil law firm for being profligate.
说曹操曹操到
Oh, here they come.
只要激进点就行
Just play the radical.
算了  我不擅长激进
Come on, I'm bad at it.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
我都怕你
You scare me.
这招对付戴安可不行
Not with Diane.
她能识破
She'll know.
-你们是在抢纳税人的钱  -不  戴安
- You are robbing the taxpayers. - No, Diane, no,
你是在暗示所谓的丢失视频里
you're implying that this so-called missing video
-含有违法的内容  -我只说了
- shows something nefarious. - I'm not saying anything
警方报告里所提及的内容
other than what the police report states.
得了  戴安  你不可能半步不让的
Come on, Diane, you know you got to give up something.
-14万  -少来这套
- $140,000. - Oh, come on.
库克县不想再受迫于这些法律诉讼
Cook county will no longer have a gun put to its head
-继而在重压之下妥协  -开玩笑  重压之下妥协
- with these lawsuits. - Seriously? Gun to its head?
像我们当事人被真枪指着头的时候
How nice to be able to talk in metaphors
你用这种暗喻真是太好了
when people like our clients have a literal gun to their head.
戴安  我明白你想用你的强势给你的新客户
Look, Diane, I understand you want to impress your new client
留下好印象  但是客观来看
with your toughness, but look at the optics.
你们三名警察  三名白人警察
You got three cops-- three white cops--
一通乱踢一个手无寸铁的孩子
Kicking the crap out of this defenseless kid.
是的  可怜无辜的偷车贼
Yes, this poor, innocent car thief.
这就是你们的策略  责怪受害者
So that's your strategy? Blame the victim?
不  我们的策略是这样的
No, this is our strategy.
贵所通过这些警方暴力执法的案件
Your firm has personally enriched itself
为自身谋取利益高达
to the tune of $180 million
1亿8000万美元
with these police brutality cases.
你们就是在抢劫
You are robbing the tax dollars
这座城市最弱势的
coming from the city's most vulnerable
美国黑人社区的纳税钱
African-american communities...
戴安  你是什么时候变得如此愤世嫉俗的
Diane, when did you get so cynical?
你应该站在我们这一边  而不是
You should be on this side of the table, not...
我们都是在利用这个案子  卢卡
We're both using this case, Lucca.
你还是就事论事的好
Why don't you just stick to the facts?
好吧  这样吧
Okay, all right.
我们降到400万
We'll come down to $4 million,
不能再少了
but that's it.
那我就提到40万
And I'll go up to $400,000.
我们明天见吧  戴安
We'll see you tomorrow, Diane.
我能问一句吗
Can I ask something?
当然  问吧
Sure, go ahead.
这个案子  我们是站在正确的一方吗
Are we on the right side on this one?
我们站在必要的一方
We are on a necessary side.
我一度笃定有罪的人
People I thought with all my heart were guilty
结果却是无辜的
turned out to be innocent.
而我坚信是圣人的人
And people I thought were saints--
他们  他们反而不是
they, um, they weren't.
这就是为什么你不能相信直觉
That's why you don't go on instinct.
多等  多听
You wait, you listen
多观察
and watch.
最终  人人都会显露本色
Eventually, everyone reveals themself.
我们正在整合资源
Hey, we're pooling our resources.
要不要一起
You want to join?
不了  谢谢
No, it's all right. Thanks.
你去哪了
Where were you?
这些我才弄了三分之一
I'm only a third of the way through this.
一个合伙人给了我一个任务
A partner just gave me an assignment
而且我可以再拽一个律师来帮我
and I can pull another associate onto it.
你想做吗
You want to do it?
想啊
Yes!
等等  等一下
Wait, hey... Wait a second,
等一下  这只是摆摆姿态而已
Wait a second. It's a pose.
做个样子  他们开价会变高的
That's all. They will come up.
我们不想在这上面耗太多时间  阿德里安
We don't want to bury too much time in this, Adrian.
芭芭拉
Barbara, look,
库克县  他们想让我们妥协
Cook county, they're trying to break our backs on this thing.
我们妥协一次  下次他们就会以之要挟
We bend here, they use it against us on the next suit.
卢卡
Lucca?
你了解戴安  你觉得她会提高报价吗
You know Diane. Will she come up in her offer?
我认为戴安要证明自己
I think Diane's got something to prove
-而且她会努力做到  -所以呢
- and she's out to prove it. - So what?
我也要证明自己
I have something to prove.
我们都要证明自己
We all have something to prove.
-她就要退休了  -是的
- She's retiring? - Yes.
她想赢下最后一战
She wants to go out with a win.
让她的报价提高到100万  然后处理别的案子吧
Let's get her up to a million, and move on to the next.
不  芭芭拉  我告诉你  她想要我们妥协
No, barbara, she wants to cave. I'm telling you.
等你说服她把报价提高到100万再说
We'll talk when you get her to a million.
卢卡
Lucca,
一点支持都不给啊
where was the support?
只是有人问了我个问题  只是如此
I was asked a question, that's all.
你觉得我不能赢过戴安
Yeah, you don't think I can take Diane down?
没有  我只是觉得我帮不上忙  这是干嘛
No, I just think I'm not helping. What is this?
找首席财务官肯德里克  带点口音
Ask for CFO kendrick, with the accent.
拜托
Oh, come on.
我在企业层面遇到了阻碍
I'm getting held up at the corporate level.
她会很高调的  打吧  帮帮我
She'll raise her tone. Come on, help me out.
博斯曼先生  我
Mr. Boseman, I...
喂  你好
Yes, hello.
阿德里安·博斯曼想要找肯德里克先生
Adrian Boseman calling for Mr. Kendrick.
如果可以的话  他也想亲自和他谈
Well, he'd love to talk to him now if he could.
可他刚出去吃午餐了
He's just popping out to lunch.
谢谢
Thank you.
好的
Okay.
做得真棒
That was fantastic!
祝你好运  戴安  我们会想念你的
以优等生的成绩毕业于法律学院之后
After graduating from law school with honors,
戴安成为了一名地区检察官助理
Diane became an Assistant District Attorney.
她以不遗余力寻求真相
She made her reputation as someone
而广受赞誉
who fought hard for the truth,
五年之后
And after five years...
天呐  我有那么年轻过吗
Oh, my god, was I ever that young?
我简直不敢相信你就要离开我们了  戴安
I can't believe you're leaving us, Diane.
我精神上与你们同在
Oh, not in spirit.
如果你想要回来的话
If you ever think of coming back,
一定要先来我这儿
You don't go anywhere else first.
我答应你  蕾妮
I promise, Renee.
等一下
Wait a minute...
你答应过我的
You promised me.
你好  伊森
Oh, Ethan.
我们是伙伴  我的大门永远为你敞开
We have partners I'd throw out the door to make room for you.
被需要的感觉真好
Wow. Well, it's... It's good to be wanted.
谢谢你的到来
Thank you for coming.
丽诺
Hi. Lenore!
看看你呀
Oh, look at you.
祝贺你
Congrats.
玛娅告诉我们你是一位良师
Maia tells us what a great mentor you are.
她是个好孩子  我爱她
Oh, she's such a doll. I love her.
顺便说一下  格伦一直想要找你
By the way, uh, Glenn's been trying to reach you.
在普罗旺斯的房子这事上我们没有时间了
We're running out of time on the Provence house.
我的天哪
Oh, my god,
我真是好嫉妒  普罗旺斯啊
I am so jealous. Provence!
是啊  但我要先给首付才行
Yeah, but only if I make the down payment.
是的  我想把事情都处理妥当
Well, yes, I wanted to get my ducks in a row first.
你的投资项目回报很高  戴安
You know, your investments are working so well for you, Diane,
我提议一个更明智的选择  首付去借贷
I was wondering if it's not smarter to borrow the money,
你的钱还是存在基金里
and leave it in the fund.
好的  那我和格伦再谈谈吧
Oh, well, let me discuss it with Glenn.
但是你可以给他打电话啊  他并不坏
But, um, do give him a call, he's not a bad guy,
而且他感觉自己被忽视了
and he's feeling a bit ignored.
是啊  会计师本来就倾向于觉得被忽视
Yeah, accountants tend to feel ignored.
-你好啊  亲爱的  -他们来了
- Hello, darling. - Oh, there they are,
强力妻妻
the power couple.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
你们俩什么时候才结婚
So when are you two getting married?
妈  别这样
Mom, no!
为什么  最高法院的借口已经行不通了
Why? There's no supreme court excuse anymore.
你和你叔叔谈了吗
Have you talked to your uncle?
谁啊  贾克斯吗  没有
Who, Jax? Mm. No.
他没和你说基金的事吗
He didn't talk to you about the fund?
没有  怎么了
No, why?
没事  只是你们两个太亲近了
Nothing, just you two are so close.
如果他给你打电话  让你和别人谈话
If he calls you and asks you to talk to anyone,
先给我打个电话  好吗
call me first, okay?
发生什么事了  爸爸
What's going on, dad?
没事  你了解贾克斯  他总是说话很狂
Nothing, you know Jax, he tends to talk kind of wild.
我不想把大家都搞疯
I don't want to make everyone crazy.
好的
Okay.
-晚安  甜心  -晚安
- Good night, honey. - Good night.
-这真是太振奋了  -卢卡
- This is so exciting. - Lucca!
请陈述你的姓名和职业  先生
Please give your name and occupation for the record, sir.
安德鲁·泰鲁  芝加哥警官  第三年在职
Andrew Theroux. CPD, three years on duty.
视频上的这个人是你吗  先生
Is this you on the video, sir?
是的  但这不是全部的情况
Yeah, but that's not the whole thing.
等下会让你解释的  这是什么
You'll get a chance to explain. What is that?
我的制服
My uniform.
不  我是说那个
No, that...
那里
There.
-我的随身摄像机  -型号是IP68
- My bodycam. - Your IP68.
三年前起  所有库克县警官都会佩戴
It was given to all Cook County officers 3 years ago,
为了预防警官吃官司  比如这个案子
in order to prevent law suit exactly like this one.
你是提问还是在陈述事实
Is there a question here or it's just a statement?
泰鲁警官
So, Officer Theroux
你的随身摄像机在拍摄现场时朝向哪里
where your bodycam video recording of this encounter?
摄像机没开
It wasn't turned on.
-不好意思  你说什么  -你听到了
- I'm sorry what? - You've heard.
事实上现场有你们三个人
In fact there were three of you there,
而你们三人的随身摄像机都没有开
and all 3 of your body cams were turned off.
怎么了
What?
你看见他们身后的那辆车了吗
Do you see that car in the background?
我爸妈也有一辆一模一样的
My parents own one just like it.
这不是他们爆窃的车
It's not the car they were breaking into.
我知道  但你看到边灯是亮着的吗
I know, but, uh, well, do you see the perimeter light on?
如果有人与车发生碰撞它就会亮
That's what happens when someone bumps it.
这车有四个车边摄像头
It has four perimeter cameras,
它们会自动录像并存在硬盘中
and they automatically record and save to its hard drive.
你是说如果我们联系到那辆车的车主
You're saying if we contact the owner of that car,
就能找到这个事件的录像了
they'll have a video of this encounter?
就在硬盘上  它们没法被清除掉
It's on its hard drive. They can't erase it.
干得漂亮
Good work!
佐伊  要调查员过来一下
Zoe, ask the investigator to come up here.
-干得漂亮  -谢谢
- Good job! - Thanks.
比起百合花  这些雏菊合我心意多了
I like these daisies much better than the lilies.
什么事
Hey, what's up?
什么
What?
搜查证
他们有搜查证
They have a warrant.
他们在搜查我们的公寓
They're searching our apartment.
他们问我们有没有银行联合账户
They're asking if we have a joint bank account.
-什么  为什么  -不知道
- What? Why? - I don't know.
他们扣留了我们的电脑
They've impounded our computers
还在找你父母的商业文件
and they're looking for documents on your parents' business.
我觉得和你爸有关
I think it's about your dad.
看看这个
Check this out.
不好意思先生们  能把那个放下吗
Excuse me gentlemen, can you put that down please?
女士  请不要打电话
Ma'am, I need you to get out of your phone.
我是助理州检察官  警官
I'm an Assistant State's Attorney, sir.
我有权利使用我的手机
I have the right to use my cell phone.
先挂断电话我们再来探讨你的权利
We'll discuss your right after you hang up your phone.
玛娅  我稍后打给你
Maia, I have to call you back.
拨打
爸爸
爸  联调局在搜查我的公寓
Dad, the FBI are searching my apartment.
他们说是跟你有关  发生什么了
They say it's about you. What's going on?
我们无法把他按在地上
We couldn't hold him down,
他肯定磕了药  否则不可能...
He was definetly hopped-up on something. There's no way...
你是说肯德尔先生当时磕了迷幻药
So, you're saying Mr. Kendall was high on PCP?
是的  他完全疯了
Yes. He was crazed,
-想夺我们的枪  -你怎么能...
- grabbing for our guns. - How could you...
你的会计师打来了
Your accountant is on the line.
告诉他我稍后回电
Tell him I'll call him back.
他说这事很重要
He says it's important.
我们培训过如何分辨
...are trained to recognize.
我们看见了他的行为...
When we saw how he was acting...
爸
Dad!
天啊
Oh, my god.
去看看你妈  没事的
Go see your mom. It's okay.
-爸  -亲爱的  听我说
- Oh, dad. - Sweetheart, listen to me.
一切都会没事的  我保证
Everything's gonna be fine, I promise.
我知道
I know.
我爱你  我没有干  玛娅
I love you. I didn't do it, Maia.
我知道  我知道
I know, I know!
格伦  发生什么了  是房子的事吗
Glenn, what's going on? Is it the house?
没有  怎么了
No, what?
什么时候
When?
我不理解  我刚才...
I don't understand, I just...
很多金融人士在问
Many on Wall Street are asking,
亿万富翁投资商亨利·林德尔被捕
亨利·林德尔是新麦道夫吗
Is Henry Rindell the new Madoff?
麦道夫：美国史上最大的诈骗案"庞氏骗局"的制造者
今日早些时候  联调局关闭了
Earlier today, the FBI shuttered
这个只有受邀才能加入的投资基金
the invitation-only investment fund,
称其为涉及数十亿美元的庞氏骗局
calling it a multibillion-dollar Ponzi scheme,
该基金的倒闭会使我国
whose collapse has decimated the accounts
许多自由派精英的账户大幅缩水
of many of the nation's liberal elites.
格伦  那我的...
Glenn, what about my...
我的退休金呢
my retirement money?
从200万到500万美元
...range from $2 to $5 million.
妈的
Fuck!
傲骨之战
第一季  第一集
这使得这次行动看起来有利且合法
This makes the operation seem profitable and legitimate
虽然并不是实体上的盈利
even though no actual profit is being made.
-你有一直在健身  -是啊
- You've been working out. - Yeah.
和其他人一起
With someone not me.
你很忙
You were busy.
涉及83亿资产
...with $8.3 billion in assets,
这将是美国历史上第四大庞氏骗局
it'll be the fourth largest Ponzi scheme in America...
我认识她
I know her.
谁  她吗
Who, her?
希望你的钱没有被卷进去
I hope you didn't have any money wrapped up with them.
我姑妈的有
My aunt did.
天啊  现在她可难做人了
God, I'd sure hate to be her right now.
说到美国人最恨的人
Talk about the most hated person in America.
庞氏骗局是由一名中心操盘手操控
...Ponzi schemes are run by a central operator,
他利用新投资者投进来的钱
who uses the money from new incoming investors
去支付给给上一批投资人作为承诺的回报
to pay off the promised returns to older ones...
一想到这个投资基金的邀请我就不寒而栗
Shuddered at the invitation of the investment fund,
这个数十亿美元的庞氏骗局...
calling it a multibillion-dollar Ponzi scheme...
丽诺
Lenore?
鲁珀特
Rupert?
你见过他了吗
Did you see him?
见过了
Yes, yes, yes.
亨利没事
Henry is fine.
太好了  太好了
Good, good.
玛娅  艾米  幸好你俩都在
Hey, Maia, Amy. I'm glad you're both here.
怎么回事
What's going on?
你的父亲需要你的帮助
Your dad needs your help.
你叔叔贾克斯刚和联调局的人达成协议
Your uncle Jax made a deal with the Feds.
天哪  他太可怕了  他说了什么
Oh, my god, he's a monster. What's he saying?
说亨利制造了这起庞氏骗局
That Henry created the ponzi scheme.
贾克斯声称自己与其毫无瓜葛
Jax claims he had nothing to do it with it.
只不过是亨利骗局的遮羞布
He was just a fig leaf for Henry's scam.
荒谬至极  那怎么可能
That is insane. That doesn't even make sense.
明明贾克斯负责股票买卖
Jax traded stocks.
我们只不过是为他宣传
We were just the ambassadors.
所以当务之急就是
That's why it's important that we all agree
我们达成共识
on our understanding here.
先从你俩开始...  玛娅
Starting with you two... Maia?
玛娅
Maia?
-在  -我们需要你的帮助
- Yeah. - We need your help.
你也是基金会董事会的成员吗
You were on the board of the foundation?
天哪  他是说基金会也牵扯其中吗
Oh, my God, is he saying that the foundation is part of this?
不  他说之前为了躲避审查
No. He's saying the money was parked there
才把钱暂时放在那儿
to hide it during audits.
所以玛娅  需要所有成员签字才能将钱转移
So, Maia, there are signatures on each one of the money transfers.
你得看一下文件
I need you to take a look at them.
我们该走了
Actually, we should go.
什么  不行  为什么
What? No, no. Why?
我们不该牵扯进来  走吧
We shouldn't be here for this. Let's go.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
我只是让玛娅在文件上签字罢了
I just need Maia to initial these documents.
鲁珀特  你是亨利和丽诺的律师
Rupert. You're Henry and Lenore's lawyer,
不是玛娅的
not Maia's.
-我是他们的家庭律师  -不是
- Well, I'm the family lawyer. - That's not true.
你和他争什么
Why are you arguing with him?
事实如此  玛娅
It is true. Maia.
你爸需要你的帮助
Dad needs your help.
他正麻烦缠身
Dad's in trouble.
玛娅  在这些文件上签字吧
Maia, just look at these documents.
鲁伯特  你我有律师与当事人的保密协定吗
Rupert, do we have attorney-client privilege?
没有  但我们受我与你母亲的保密协议保护
Well, no, but we're covered by your mom's privilege.
你我有律师与当事人的保密协定吗
Do we have attorney-client privilege?
没有  但是...
N-no, but...
那你就不是我的律师
You're not my lawyer, then.
妈  我爱你
Mom, I love you.
-不是你爸做的  -我知道  我知道
- Dad didn't do this. - I know. I know.
这会要他的命
This will kill him.
我们不答应
We won't let it.
天哪  知道这意味着什么吗
God, what does this mean? Um...
意味着我基本失去了半辈子的积蓄
It means I basically lost half my life.
我无法退休
I don't have a retirement.
我和妻子必须工作到死
My wife and I will have to work until we drop dead.
他们都该进监狱  每一个人
They should go to jail, every single one of 'em.
就连他们的女儿也是  她肯定知情
Even the daughter. She had to know, too.
我白白工作了二十年
I-I just worked 20 years for no reason.
我和丈夫会失去我们的房子
My husband and I will lose our house,
车子  所有一切
our cars, everything.
我们的孩子也将一无所有
Our kids will have nothing.
我们失去了奋斗得来的一切  几乎所有人
We've lost everything that we've worked for. Almost everyone...
要说出来太难了
That was hard.
你做得很好
You did good.
这是噩梦
It's a nightmare.
你需要一个律师
You're gonna need a lawyer.
戴安
Diane?
怎么了
Yes?
你在听我说吗
Are you hearing this?
全都没了
It's all gone?
林德尔家族现在手头只有1380万
Well, the Rindells have $13.8 million on hand,
而初始投资金有80亿
and that's from an initial investment of $8 billion.
他们一分钱都没投资吗
They never invested a cent?
2008年之后就没有了
Not after 2008.
房地产泡沫曾使资金出现短缺
The housing bubble. There was a shortfall,
他们用新投资者的钱填补了空缺
and they made it up with money from new investors.
我还介绍了客户给他们
But I steered people to them.
女性基金会  她们所有的钱
The women's fund, all their money.
我甚至让艾米丽的客户把养老金都了投进去
I even told Emily's list to put their 401k there.
我知道你有很多伤脑筋的事  戴安
I know there's a lot for you to process, Diane,
但有些事我们得先考虑
but we need to think about a few things
并且动作要快
and act fast.
-第三方托管的事吗  -没错
- The escrow? - Yes.
尽管会有惩罚
There will be a penalty,
但我们必须马上抽身
but we must get out of it now.
光之墅
的确
Yes.
很好
Good.
你还需要推迟退休
And you need to delay your retirement.
政府可能冻结你的账户
The government might freeze your account
把你列入最低生活工资名单
and put you on a living-wage budget.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
他们要设法将过去的收益追回
Well, they can claw back past earnings
再分配给所有的受害者
and distribute them among all the victims.
麦道夫事件时他们就是这么处理的
That's what they did with Madoff.
可我的个人账户  那是我自己的钱啊
But my personal account-- that is my money, isn't it?
不一定
No, not necessarily.
他们会允许你保留
They'll allow you to keep
能维持最低生活水平的现金
a subsistence-level amount of cash,
但可能会冻结剩余的
but they might freeze the rest.
所以我破产了吗
So am I broke?
我不太喜欢这个说法
Well, I don't like to talk that way,
但你一直以来享有的生活
but you can't live the way you've been living
持续不了几个月了
for more than a few months.
你得保住你的工作
You'll need to keep your job.
或者把你的公寓转租出去
Or maybe sublet this apartment.
你和你丈夫还没办离婚
Is there a reason you and your husband
是有什么原因吗
are delaying your divorce?
什么
What?
你和你丈夫不是分居了吗
You and your husband are separated, right?
-没错  -如果是永久分居
- Yes.  - Well, if your separation is permanent,
你们就应该认真考虑一下
then you really should consider
是否该完成离婚手续了
memorializing with the divorce,
不然他的账户也有可能被冻结
otherwise, his accounts could be frozen, too.
这真是太可怕了
This is a nightmare.
再说一遍  你得先下手为强
Again, you need to act first.
你要做的第一件事就是延后你的退休计划
And the first thing is to delay your retirement.
这不单是因为我的财政状况
This is not just about my financial situation.
也因为我怕自己会想念当律师的日子
I'm also afraid I would miss practicing the law.
我当时正在给肯德尔案取证
I was in the midst of the Kendall deposition,
心里突然想  天哪
And I thought, uh, my god,
我爱这一行  我就是干这一行的
I love this-- this is what I do.
所以你有什么提议
So what do you propose?
我不退休了  等结案之后
That I not leave. That I close the case,
我继续留在这里
and, um, that I stay on.
什么职位
In what position?
这个职位  我现在的职位
This position. My-my current position.
你已经签了离职协议了
You signed your exit agreement.
是的  但我们可以先不理那一点书面协议
Well, yes, but I would suggest we rip that up for the moment.
只可惜  我们应该没法接受
Unfortunately, I don't think that works for us.
为什么
Why not?
如你所说  我们的管理层有点太臃肿了
Well, we're kind of top-heavy, like you said.
我们已经根据你的离职重新做出调整
We already reorganized around your leaving.
这是我的律所啊
This is my firm.
不  这曾是你的律所
No, it was your firm.
是这样的  如果你想退休后保留职称
Look, if you want to stay on as an emeritus,
我们可以好好商量
we can discuss that.
然后放弃我的股权吗
And lose my equity?
你们不怕我带着客户离开这里吗
What is to keep me from taking my clients out the door with me?
你能把客人带到哪里去
Where would you take them?
我刚帮你们签下库克县这个一年3200万的大客户
I just brought Cook County and their 32 million a year to you.
等客户走了  我看你们有什么反应
Let's see how you feel when you lose them.
你就是那个女人  对不对
You are her, aren't you?
不是
No.
你是林德尔家族的
You're a Rindell.
你们害得我的退休金全没了
I lost my retirement because of you.
抱歉  我要...
Excuse me, I have to...
我知道你在哪里上班  蠢婊子
I know where you work, you stupid bitch!
你以为这事结束了吗
You think this is over?
-林德尔女士  -我和那件事无关...
- Ms. Rindell.  - I have nothing to do with...
不  我叫耶什·曼奇尼
No, I'm Yesha Mancini.
我是你的律师
I'm your lawyer.
你好  这里是洛哈特&德克尔...
Good morning, Lockhart, Deckler...
你多大了
How old are you?
这很重要吗
Does that matter?
有时挺重要的
It can.
Twenty-five.
-你当多久律师了  -6个月
- And you've been a lawyer for?  - Six months.
比我多3个月
Three months longer than me.
你联系了我们律所  说想雇一名律师
Uh, you contacted my firm asking for a lawyer.
不  那是我女友打的电话
No, my girlfriend did.
你女朋友想在我们律所请一名律师
Your girlfriend contacted my firm asking for a lawyer.
大家都很忙  所以...
Everyone else was busy, so...
我来了
tag...I'm it.
我想我们该谈一些...
I think we need to talk about a few things...
我得回去上班了
I got to get back.
等联调局找你去录口供的时候
Uh, when the Feds call you in for an interview...
他们肯定会的  记得打给我
and they will...call me.
这是我的名片
Here's my card.
其实这是我们律所的名片
Actually, it's my firm's card.
我把我老板的名字换成我的了
I just scratched out my boss' name. That's mine right there.
阿姆斯特朗&海耶斯&拉加德律所
耶什·曼奇尼律师
这可没给我多少信心啊
Doesn't really instill confidence.
下次会给你我自己的名片
I'll have cards made up for next time.
我仔细考虑了你之前在派对上说的话
So, um, I was thinking about what you said at the party.
你说为了给我腾出位子
That you would have partners
会踢走一部分合伙人
thrown out the door to make room for me.
你是想当荣誉合伙人吗
Now, you're looking for an emeritus position?
不  是合伙人
Uh, no, a partnership.
我是说  我没...
I mean, I'm not...
想着让律所门口挂着我的名字  但...
looking for my name on the door, but...
我还是先和合伙人商量看看吧
Well, let me talk to my partners.
我仔细想了想你那天在我的派对上说的话
So I was thinking about what you said at my party,
我突然想到  为什么不继续当律师呢
And I realized-- why am I leaving the law?
我们还没打破天花板效应呢
We're not done breaking the glass ceiling.
女性晋升高管的隐形屏障
-你不退休了吗  -不退了
- You're not retiring? - No.
但我确实要离开现在的律所了
But I am leaving my old firm.
我希望能加入你们
I was, um, hoping to join you.
发生什么了  蕾妮
What's going on, Renee?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我今天都和三家律所谈过了
I've been to three firms today.
要是在一个月前  他们早就高兴坏了
A month ago, they would've been climbing all over themselves.
现在时机不是很好  戴安
Uh... It's a tough time, Diane.
不是那样的  你在瞎说屁话
No, it's not. That's bullshit.
你说话能文明点吗
Do you want a civil conversation?
我希望朋友间说话能坦诚点
I want an honest conversation with a friend.
戴安  你也老大不小了
Diane, you're not a spring chicken.
所以因为我年纪大了  那么多客户都不要了
Oh, so it's ageism, with my book of clients?
那你就联系他们  戴安
Call them, Diane.
看看有多少客户肯跟你走
How many will actually go with you?
看看有多少人因为林德尔一家亏了钱
How many lost money with the Rindells?
又不是我骗了他们的钱
I'm not the Rindells.
是你把他们介绍给大家的
You referred them to people.
芝加哥女性基金会
The Chicago Women's Fund?
亏了整整8200万
It's out $82 million.
他们也许得关门大吉了
They may have to close their doors.
就给自己点时间吧
Just give it some time.
现在时机不对  你当下就好比毒药
It's a bad time right now. You're poison.
没有律所会雇佣你的
No firm will hire you.
就让这件事慢慢过去吧
Just let it pass.
你想要离婚吗
You want a divorce?
你的会计给我打过电话了
Your accountant called.
不离婚的话  库尔特
Without a divorce, Kurt,
你的财产将会受到同样的
your finances will suffer from the same, uh...
同样的
from the same...
处置
thing.
这事关财产  和我俩无关
It's about money, not about us.
你希望怎样
What do you want?
不  这事
No, this is...
这事决定权在你
this is in your lap.
我并没有离开你
I didn't leave you.
实际上  你就是这么做了
Actually, you did.
你睡了你的学生  所以
You slept with your student, so...
好了  我的会计说
Okay, my accountant said that
我的银行账户会被冻结
my bank account will be frozen.
离婚会让你的账户免受牵连
A divorce will, uh, save your account
也算是签字确认我们当前的生活状态
and just memorialize what we're doing now.
什么状态
Which is?
分居
Living apart.
你还好吗
How are you?
我好极了
I'm great.
我现在破产而且失业
I'm broke and out of a job,
但是
But, hey...
不幸的事情就是会发生在好人身上
bad things happen to good people.
你失业了
You're out of a job?
是的  我已经签了离职协议  而他们
Yes, I signed my exit agreement, and they...
他们不愿
...they won't...
上帝啊
Oh, my god.
这就是我的生活  而现在
This is my life, and it's...
全完了
it's over.
什么都没了
It's gone.
我将要失去我的公寓
I'm losing my apartment.
我不宜被雇佣  这怎么可能
I'm unemployable. How is that possible?
我的生活怎么就他妈一下子变得如此毫无意义
How is my life suddenly so fucking meaningless?!
不是这样的
It isn't.
一个人是怎样每一天都努力辛勤工作
How can you work so hard every single day of your life
到头来却没有任何东西去证明价值
and have nothing to show for it?
甚至连一个朋友都没有
Not a friend!
我就是你朋友啊
I'm a friend.
库尔特
Kurt?
我已经感觉够糟糕了
I feel bad enough already.
我不想再承担
I don't want to be responsible
让你破产的责任了
for your going broke.
和我离婚吧
Divorce me.
早上好
Good morning,
这里是洛哈特&德克尔&古斯曼&李&莱曼&
Lockhart, Deckler, Gussman, Lee, Lyman,
吉尔伯特&卢瑞&卡根&坦纳鲍姆律所
Gilbert-Lurie, Kagan, Tannebaum & Associates.
戴安  我真的很抱歉
Diane. I am so sorry.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
那要看情况了  我能拿回我的钱吗
That depends-- will I get my money back?
抱歉  我的律师叫我
I'm sorry, my lawyer's directed me
不要回答这个问题
not to answer that.
那就别问我
Then don't ask me.
我们现在或许找到了一个小突破口
We may have a little opening right here.
去直击要害吧
Go for the jugular.
肯德尔先生  告诉我们一下你想偷
Mr. Kendall, tell us which car in the parking lot
-停车场里的哪辆车  -反对
- you were hoping to steal. - Objection.
这是个完全合理的问题
It is a completely fair question.
假设不在证据中的事实  完全没有证据支持
Not in evidence. Not close to being in evidence.
能让我把问题问完吗
Can I ask my question, please?
当然  我只是把我的反对意见记录在案
Sure, I'm just preserving my objection for the record.
是哪辆车  肯德尔先生
Which car was it, Mr. Kendall?
是图中那辆跑车吗
Was it the sports car here?
就是警察们发现车窗被砸破的那辆车
That's the one they found with the window broken.
我不  我不知道
Uh, I don't-I don't know.
我记不得了
I-I don't remember.
你不记得你当时是要偷哪辆车吗
You don't remember which car you were there to steal?
拜托  戴安
Come on, Diane,
这就是你仅有的本事了吗
Is this what you're left with--
纠缠一个坐轮椅的人
badgering someone in a wheelchair?
抱歉
Excuse me,
对纠缠证人这一说法提出反对
Objection as to badgering.
我知道你现在生活很不如意
I understand you're not happy with your life,
但别把火撒在我们当事人身上
But don't take it out on our client.
好吧  今天到此为止
Okay, we're done here.
你在这啊
There you are.
我想让这整个律所知道是她偷走了我的钱财
I want this firm to know she stole my money.
我的孩子们不能去上大学了
My kids are not going to college
就因为她偷走了我的积蓄
because she stole my savings.
你是难逃法网的  我要为了我失去的每一分
You can't get away! I'm gonna sue you
血汗钱起诉你
for every single cent!
那就去起诉啊
Then do it!
不过现在  给我滚
But right now, fuck off!
当他们看到你哭泣
When they see you cry,
就会让他们很开心
it makes them happy.
所以在这里把委屈都发泄出来
So get it out of your system here.
你是对方律师
You're on the other side.
我曾有个朋友
I had a friend.
经历了同样的遭遇
Went through the same thing.
说过了几个月地狱般的生活
Said it was hell for a few months.
坚强起来
Harden yourself.
不要理会别人怎么说
Ignore what people say.
埋头好好工作
Keep your head down and keep working.
你是刚入行的律师对吗
You're a new associate?
工作是你的好朋友
Work is your friend.
不要看电视  不要上网
Don't watch TV, don't look at the internet.
看书吗
Do you have a book?
那就看书
Then read it.
随身带着
Keep it with you at all times.
不要有眼神交流
Don't give them the satisfaction
满足他们的猎奇心
of making eye contact.
是很难
It's hard.
但总会过去
But it ends.
这是录像视频  洛哈特女士
That's the video, Mrs. Lockhart.
说什么
Excuse me?
汽车上的录像视频  你要找的
The car video. The one you asked for.
对了
Oh, right.
博斯曼先生来见你
Oh, and, uh, Mr. Boseman is here to see you.
他...什么
He... what?
我们有约吗
Did we have a negotiation?
没有
No.
好  给我点时间
Okay, give me a minute.
阿德里安
Adrian.
我不记得我们有约
I didn't know we had a meeting.
不  没有
No, no, we didn't.
也不算正式会议
Uh, we're not.
我是来聊天的
I'm here to chat.
你还好吗  戴安
How you doing, Diane?
拜托  表同情这种事不像你  阿德里安
Come on, sympathy doesn't suit you, Adrian.
有何需要
What do you need?
你
You.
我
Me?
I...
想要你加入我们律所
want you to join our firm.
你破产了  戴安
You're broke, Diane.
正在找新东家
You're looking for a place to land...
然而因为林德尔丑闻
And nobody wants you
没人想要你
'cause of this Rindell scandal.
我累了  阿德里安  我想回家
I'm tired, Adrian. I want to go home.
我们律所正在扩张
You know, we're in the midst of expanding.
你可以算是满足员工多元化的聘用
You could be... our diversity hire.
如果你是说这件案子
Well, if this is about the case,
并不能改变什么
it doesn't make any difference.
即使我加入你  我知道什么也不能说
I mean, even if I joined you, I can't use what I know.
跟这件案子无关
It's not about this case.
重要的是下一个  再下一个
It's about the next one and the next one
再下一个案子
and the next one and the next one.
戴安
Diane...
我们不想你打败我们
We don't want you to beat us.
我更想让你帮我们打败他们
I would much rather you help us beat them.
我会以合伙人的身份加入
I'd be a partner?
是  且你将再次支持正义
Yes, and you'd be back on the right side of things.
你怎么不怕林德尔丑闻
Why aren't you afraid of the Rindell scandal?
我有毒  你没听说吗
I'm poison. Haven't you heard?
主要的是  戴安
Yeah, here's the thing, Diane.
林德尔家族的投资基金
The Rindells ran an...
只邀请特定人群的加入
invitation-only investment fund, and you know what?
他们从没邀请过黑人
They never invited black folk.
你被耍了  戴安
You got fucked here, Diane.
最好的回应是什么
And you know the best response?
跟我走  反操他们一着
You come with me, and you fuck 'em back.
-给我解释一下  -好
- Explain it to me... - Okay.
-你干了什么  -我干了...
- What did you do? - I... What did I...
我这是改变策略  这叫策略  芭芭拉
I called an audible. It was an audible, Barbara. Ugh.
装得真事儿似的
Don't act like that's a thing here.
-你不商量就做了决定  -不
- You made a decision by Fiat. - Mm-mm, no.
-毫不在乎其他合伙人的想法  -不
- You didn't care what the rest of the partners thought. - No!
我看到了机会
I saw an opportunity.
-我认为这个机会...  -什么机会
- And I thought it was an opportunity that... - What opportunity?
-我们都会感激  -什么机会
- ...we would all appreciate. - What opportunity?
从此以后每次警察施暴案
Diane Lockhart's firm will be representing Cook county
戴安·洛哈特的律所都将代表
on every single one of their police brutality cases
库克县
from here until eternity!
现在至少
Now, at the very least,
我们挖走他们最强的律师
we just stole away their strongest attorney.
她可以帮我们制定策略
At the most, she helps us with strategy.
她什么都不能透露
She can't tell us anything.
这件案子不能透露
Not on this case she can't,
但以后的其它案子就可以了
but on every other case going forward she can.
芭芭拉
Barbara,
你担心失去我们的律所文化吗
are you worried about losing the firm's culture or something?
如果这是你担心的
If that's what you're worried about
-可以确保...  -阿德里安  打住
- ...we can make sure... - Adrian, stop.
你想知道我的担心吗
You want to know what I'm worried about?
-是的  -我听到的流言
- Yeah, yes, I do. - Every rumor I hear...
都说洛哈特不守本分
about Lockhart is that she doesn't know her place.
如果她不打入律所内部  就不会甘心
She's not gonna be happy until she's in the inner circle.
这是在说你自己  芭芭拉
You're describing yourself, Barbara.
这也是在说我
You're describing me.
我们有野心  需要这种人的加入
We're ambitious people, and we need people like that...
-律所才能扩张  -卢卡
- ...around to grow this company. - Lucca.
没错  但我们不需要
Yes, but we don't want people who are only happy
只想下命令的人
when they're giving orders.
卢卡  你与戴安·洛哈特共事过
Lucca, you worked with Diane Lockhart.
是的  共事一年
Yeah, for a year.
这么问毫无益处  芭芭拉
This is not helpful, Barbara.
你喜欢与她共事吗
Did you like working with her?
那不重要
I don't think it mattered.
她是合伙人  我只是律师
She was a partner; I was an associate.
是  如果她来这  一样如此
Yes, and if she came here, it would be the same thing.
你觉得如何
Would you like that here?
老天爷  帮帮我吧
Oh, God, Jesus. God, help me.
这何时变成这儿的标准了
Since when is that the criteria here?
卢卡
Lucca?
是否该让戴安加入成为合伙人
Should we bring in Diane as a partner?
是的
Yes.
为什么
Why?
因为她是个能干的律师
She's a good lawyer.
热忱  心怀大道又经验老道
She's passionate, idealistic and cunning.
还需要我什么事情吗
Anything else?
没有了
No.
她会是律所不可多得之宝
She would be an asset.
多谢了
Thanks.
这样嘛
Well...
和我预料的发展方向相反呢
...that went in a different direction than I thought.
不能让她当冠名合伙人
She can't be a name partner.
我没说让她当冠名合伙人
I didn't offer her that.
初级合伙人即可
Junior partner is fine.
还有与初级合伙人相匹配的股权
With an equal equity draw.
别再擅自改变策略了
Don't you ever call an audible again.
没问题
You got it.
天啊  他们说手上
Oh, my God, they're saying
有我们的性爱视频
they have a sex tape of us.
TMZ独家视频
"TMZ, Exclusive footage:
玛娅·林德尔女同性爱视频
Maia Rindell lesbian sex tape."
别看了  关掉它
Oh, God, don't look at it. Just close it.
天  这简直就是激将法
Oh, my God, it's like waving a red flag at a bull.
玛娅·林德尔女同性爱视频
我瞬间就变成诱惑拉拉的狐狸精了
Suddenly I'm a lesbian temptress?
这根本就不是我们  这人还有纹身
This isn't even us. This person has a tattoo.
好了听我说  你要保持镇静  好吗
Okay, listen to me, you have to stay sane, okay?
你得无视掉这些东西
You have to ignore this stuff.
明眼人都知道他们全都在撒谎
They're obviously lying. All of 'em, right?
他们整个家族都是
The whole family.
你要走了
Are you leaving?
是的
Yes.
去哪里
For where?
另一家律所
Another firm.
我不想离婚
I don't want a divorce.
或许是明智之举  但是我  我并不想要
Maybe it's smart, but I... I don't want it.
他们会冻结你的账户的
They'll freeze your account.
冻结就冻结吧
Let 'em.
库尔特  你不是一个牛仔啊
Kurt, you're not a cowboy.
我们不是生活在牛仔随心所欲的世界里
We don't live in a world with cowboys.
我不想要一点挽回的余地都没有
I don't want the door to close completely.
我们之间已经没有挽回的余地了
It is closed between us.
那你去提离婚好了
Then divorce me.
反正我这边不会提的
But I won't do it.
我父母看到了那个视频
My parents saw the tape.
他们认为是我们在做爱
They think it's us having sex.
告诉他们不是真的
Tell them it's not.
他们不相信我
They don't believe me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我要去雷迪克&博斯曼了
I'm going to Reddick & Boseman.
什么
What?
我要离开这里跳去雷迪克&博斯曼了
I'm leaving here and going to Reddick & Boseman.
有一堆黑鬼的那个律所
Oh, the bunch of schvartzes?
你不能这么做
You can't do that.
我当然可以
Yes, I can.
你如果给他们机要信息
You give them proprietary information,
我们就告你
we'll sue you.
我不需要这么做
I don't need to.
那么你一直在跟着的
Well, what about the police brutality case
警察虐待案怎么办
You've been working on?
这个就交给你处理了
I'm handing it off to you.
还有你估计得看看这个
Oh, and you may want to look at this.
警察们没有被挑衅哦
The police were unprovoked.
我可能会有估算误差  但看来
I could be wrong, but it looks like
600万在向我招手
a $6 million payout to me.
总之  再见了
Anyway, good-bye.
我在这里挺开心的
It was fun.
要我关门吗
Want the door closed?
能请你站起来吗
Could you please stand up?
站那儿去
Stand over there.
桌上有任何你的东西吗
Is there anything on this desk that is yours?
没有
Uh, no.
对了  听说你被炒鱿鱼了
Oh, hey, I heard you got fired.
真可惜  之前我还觉得花儿挺漂亮的
Too bad, I thought the flowers looked good.
阿德里安  我是戴安
Adrian, it's Diane.
几个小时内你将会接到来自这个律所的电话
In a few hours you're gonna get a call from this firm
他们会就肯德尔受虐案提出一个漂亮的和解费
Offering you a good deal on the Kendall brutality case.
是的  我认可
Yes, I don't disagree.
我只是想让你知道  找到关键证据的
I, um, I just want you to know, there's an associate here
是这儿的一个律师
Who found the key piece of evidence
是整个案子的转折点
that the case turned on,
然而她刚刚被炒了
and she was just fired.
你忘东西了
You left this.
给需要的人吧
Give it to someone who needs it.
我不干了
I'm done.
瞎说什么呢
No, you're not.
走吧
Let's go.
去哪里
Where?
某个地方
Someplace.
为什么
Why?
因为还没完呢
Because it's not over yet.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供学习  禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
公告     人人视频[人人美剧]盗用本组名号  请抵制
翻译     Alex  秋乙一  Margaery  半半子七  吃冰棒
翻译     ABCpril  杨爱菜  dzysteven  charcie  情迷偽優
校对     free维塔
时间轴     Avis  chance-coco
后期     你是不是饿得慌
总监     free维塔
最新海外影视剧下载